So finally friends, you will see that ICICI LB
Board has disclosed its Quarter 3, sorry
Quarter 4 numbers.
Brother, how were its numbers for quarter 4
and what impact can
we see on the stock,
we will discuss that in this video.  Along with this, the
final dividend has also been
declared by the company which will be ₹7
from equity shares.  That means
you will get ₹7 as dividend on every share.
Apart from this, no other special
announcement seems to be happening inside it.
Let us take a look at its
results and what impact it will have on the
stock tomorrow.
So here you will see that now we
will discuss its audited results.
All figures in lakhs
given data will be converted into cores.   Right now
here you will see the quarter ended and
year ended results.  If we talk about
total income or total revenue, then the
total income that we are seeing in the current quarter is
approximately
58, sorry, 58517
lakhs and if we convert it into crores then it will
become 5851 crores, what was it in the previous year, it was
5882 crores and
in the same quarter of the previous year it was 5100 65 crores, that is,
year to year you will see that its income has
dropped, sorry, it has increased, but on the
basis of why, its income has been
seen dropping.  Apart from this, you will
see what are its expenses i.e. the
total expenses incurred by the company
?  So the expenses in the current quarter are Rs
54,53,35 crore.
Ok?  What was it in the previous year, it was Rs 5197
crore and Rs 463 crore in the same quarter of the previous year.  That
means there is an
expense increase from the same quarter of the previous year.  And
you will see that there is an increase in expenses from the previous quarter also.
And this time, not only the
revenue, but the expenses are also
high.  Meaning the company
made profit but how much is the profit?  Let's see
if we talk about Net Profit After Tax,
then you will see here that it is 509 crores
which was 724 crores in the previous year and
519 crores in the same quarter of the previous year, that is,
year to year and quarter to
quarter its profit has been
seen declining and because
on this basis its revenues have also fallen brother, so
we can see its negative impact on the stock
and the rest of its market estimates are
not available brother, here you will
see its Earnings per Share i.e.
EPS is ₹1.29 which was 1463 in the previous year
and ₹1055 in the same quarter of the previous year,
apart from this you will see
what other announcements are there below, there are
no special updates right now, okay,
these notes are given, you
must read them once, by pausing the video
what other updates have been there during the quarter,
you will get to see the data here,
right now dividend
I have told you about the revenue
segment etc., you can see here
how much revenue the company has generated from which segment.
Ok?  You will get
to see the data here.  And if you have any other questions, you
can ask in the comments and read the notes.
If you have shares of the company
or are thinking of investing,
you will get detailed information here.
And thank you for watching the